aadharcarduid.com 2014-06-25

# AadharCardUID.com Privacy Policy

* * *

By using this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the [Terms of Use and Disclaimer](http://aadharcarduid.com/disclaimer). AadharCardUID.com collects certain information about you that you specifically and knowingly provide to us, such as your user name, email address, name or mailing address. In addition, we may track how you use this website and relate it to the information you have provided to us. If you wish to be notified of the use of such tracking software and/or disable such software ("cookies"), your browser may offer this feature by means of its options or preferences menu.

The above-described information (Personally-Identifying Information) may be used by AadharCardUID.com to personalize and enhance your use of this website, including the marketing and promotion of certain products and services that might be of interest to you. Your use of this website is a consent to the foregoing use of your Personally-Identifying Information by AadharCardUID.com.

AadharCardUID.com also may share your Personally-Identifying Information with select companies and organizations for their own marketing and promotional use. While AadharCardUID.com seeks to share Personally-Identifying Information with companies that follow appropriate privacy policies, it does not bear any responsibility for the actions and policies of such third parties. If you wish that we not share your Personally-Identifying Information with third parties, you may "opt out" by emailing us (@ [info@aadharcarduid.com](mailto:info@aadharcarduid.com)) with such request.

You should be aware that any Personally-Identifying Information, such as your user name and email address, as well as any other information that you post on a bulletin board, share in a "chat room," or otherwise specifically and knowingly disclose by use of the Forums, may be directly collected and used by third parties. Therefore, you may be subject to unsolicited email as a result of your disclosure of such information. You should have no expectation of privacy with respect to your communications through the forums. 

* * *

### Your Privacy

By uploading files or data onto the website, or otherwise providing information on or through the website (each, a "submission"), you are granting AadharCardUID.com. a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, worldwide license to: use, copy, adapt, transmit, publicly perform, display or distribute the submission, without limitation.

Your continued use of this website constitutes your acceptance of these terms and conditions of use as well as our Privacy Policy and waiver of liability on the part of AadharCardUID.com.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

* * *

### Privacy Policy for Advertisements

The [DoubleClick cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?answer=2839090) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their website(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party vendors and ad networks to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).
